misterart.com 2019-11-14

# MisterArt.com About Us | Shop Art Supplies, Craft Supplies

### PRIVACY POLICY

MisterArt.com is owned by MisterArt.com LP (“MisterArt”, “we”, “us”, “our”). At MisterArt, we are committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of contact information you share with us (the phrase "contact information" means any information by which you can be contacted or personally identified, such as your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review, correct and opt out of our use of, the information. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect about you through our website and mobile applications. By using our web site, mobile applications, or sharing your contact information with us, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

As a part of our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to (i) honor customers' requests not to share their contact information with other marketers; and (ii) honor customers' requests not to receive mail, telephone, or other solicitations from MisterArt and its affiliates and brands.

### COLLECTING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product, subscribe to a service, or participate in promotions, etc.) when we ask you to provide certain contact information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, social media user name, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, and other information. We may also maintain a record of your product purchases.

Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. However, if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our web site. In addition, we may need to contact you via phone, email or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you have opted to not receive marketing communications from us.

In general, you can visit our web site without telling us who you are or revealing any contact information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us, other electronic markers and identifiers and other information about our site and mobile app traffic. We may analyze this data for preferences, trends, site usage statistics and to recognize you. We may also receive usage data from your mobile phone or other device you use to access our web site or our mobile applications, including location data, which we may also combine with other information.

If you access any of our website or mobile applications with your log-in credentials from a social networking site (e.g., facebook or twitter) or if you otherwise agree to associate your account with us with a social networking site, we may receive personal information about you from such social networking site, in accordance with the terms of use and privacy policy of the social networking site. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via our website and mobile applications.

### USING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

We use your contact information for analytical and marketing purposes, such as:

  * confirming and tracking your order, subscription, or registration;
  * analyzing preferences, trends, and statistics;
  * informing you of our new products, services, and offers; and
  * providing you with other information from and about MisterArt and its brands and affiliates.

We contact you only in ways compatible with your communication choices.

From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy. In such cases we might share and/or cross-reference information, including contact information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with others, including providers of third party cookie and other third party browsing and use data. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize the shopping experience of you and others with us, and to recognize our customers so that we can communicate with you directly about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

We may contract with companies or persons (“Service Providers”) to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data analysis and management, promotional services, etc. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services.

We may allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. Several of these third party companies who may utilize these cookies or beacons on our web site enable you to opt out of this behavioral advertising. We also provide you with additional tools to opt out of marketing from us or certain transfers of your information. You can learn about this in the "Opting Out of Marketing and Transfers" section of this Privacy Policy.

In certain instances we may disclose your contact information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to MisterArt and/or its brands and affiliates, or to others. We may also disclose your contact information when we believe the law or legal process requires it.

### OPTING OUT OF MARKETING AND TRANSFERS; UPDATING AND DELETING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive direct marketing from us or from our affiliates, partners, or Service Providers, please let us know by contacting us at 800-721-3015 or by sending us an email to [cs@misterart.com](mailto:cs@misterart.com). Please be sure to include your full name, email address, mailing address, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing address or other contact information with us please contact us the same way. If you wish, you may use one of the following statements in your message to us:

  * I prefer not to receive email advertisements, such as updates regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events.
  * I prefer not to have my contact information provided to third parties for their marketing purposes.

You may also click the designated link at the bottom of all email advertisements to be removed from future email updates.

Please note that it may take up to 10 days for us to accommodate any emailed requests to remove or update your contact information.

### COOKIES

When you visit our web site, we send one or more "cookies" to your computer or other device. We may also use cookies in emails that you receive from us. A "cookie" is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a web site. A "session cookie" expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A "persistent cookie" stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same web site at a later date the cookie information is still available. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service when you visit our web site and other web sites of interest to you. We also use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products, services and advertising to suit the personal interests of you and others, estimate our audience size, assist our online merchants to track visits to and sales at our web site and to process your order, track your status in our promotions and contests, and/or analyze your visiting patterns.

Certain of our Service Providers may use cookies and collect information on our behalf. In addition, we or certain of our Service Providers, in connection with the services that they provide to us, may work with third parties who may use cookies to collect information to tailor advertising for you and others elsewhere on the Internet and on our web site, and to assist in reminding us of who you are. If you would like to opt out of accepting cookies altogether, you can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. However, certain features of our web site or other services may not work if you delete or disable cookies.

### SECURITY

We maintain electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. To guard your information delivered to us electronically, our web site uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL encrypts your credit card number, name and address so only we are able to decode your information. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your contact information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web site, and you do so at your own risk.

We urge you to keep any password that you establish with us in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.

### PROTECTING CHILDREN

Our web site is for general audiences and is not intended for use by anyone under the age of 18. Children under the age of 18 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any contact information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's access to the Internet.

California users under the age of 18 may request the removal of their content or information publicly posted on our web site or mobile applications by sending us an email to [cs@misterart.com](mailto:cs@misterart.com).

### LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

Our web site may contain links to web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any of your information on such site.

### POLICY CHANGES

We may change our Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on MisterArt.com to inform you of the same. Those changes will go into effect on the effective date posted in the revised Privacy Policy. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our web sites and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. 

Your continued use of our web site or other services constitutes your acceptance of the practices described in the revised Privacy Policy.

### YOUR FEEDBACK

To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. You may email us at [cs@misterart.com](mailto:cs@misterart.com) or call us at 800-721-3015.

### LEGAL STATEMENT

All of the materials, including images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, video clips, writing, and other materials that appear on this website (collectively, the "Contents") are subject to copyright, trademark, service mark, trade dress and other intellectual property rights or licenses held by MisterArt. Your use of the trademarks, service marks, trade dress and copyrighted material displayed on this website is strictly prohibited.

You may not copy, download, reproduce, modify, publish, distribute, transmit, distribute display, transfer, create derivative works from, sell or participate in the sale of, or exploit in any way, in whole or in part, any of the Contents, the site, or any related software.
